Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
=Blemish Flaw=
=Episode 16=
During the release on bail,
get plenty of rest.
I know.
You can't get rid of the wheelchair yet.
It's fine. I'm used to it.
I prefer this over walking.
In about a year,
I'll find a doctor
to treat your legs.
No rush.
"No rush"?
You're almost 30.
Isn't it great?
I'm only 30,
and I've figured everything out.
No one can ever
figure everything out.
Even I haven't achieved that
at my age.
Let's take our time then.
Cheers.
Mr. Bai,
your reward.
I won't tell Mom.
Actually,
I kept this
from your mom on purpose.
I want her to keep nagging me.
Or she'll be bored.
(The future is wide open)
You finally
came out for food.
(Why so anxious)
I finally have
some days off.
Right,
we found Lin Fang's body.
Zeng Jie has been
convicted of murder.
Lin Shan
is charged with harboring and extortion.
Now you can rest assured.
I know
the law is just.
I'm happy for Bai Xiaoling.
You went to see her?
Why do you look
exhausted?
We've been extremely busy
these days.
What's there to be busy about?
I can't share the details,
but I'm sure that something's wrong
and the truth
will be revealed.
(Good fortune)
Bravo!
Are you saying...
Big Hui,
I'm saying this because I trust you.
You've made many
analytical videos
and feel confident.
But I'm afraid I must
bring you down.
The gap between professional
and amateur work is enormous.
You and your fans might
think your analyses
are spot on,
but in fact,
your videos
are built on
solved cases.
The real investigation,
you know,
is extremely tedious.
We often spend months
conducting interviews
just to obtain a sliver of information.
It gets reduced
to a single line:
"After relentless police efforts",
and that's it.
The way you jump to conclusions
makes it exciting.
Many movies
and TV shows portray
police officers smoking a cigarette
and thinking for a moment,
then having an epiphany
to crack the case.
How is that possible in real life?
All we can do
is minimize errors
and oversight,
and deduce through all the clues
and evidence.
Not with whimsical guesses.
That's the difference
between the amateurs
and professionals?
No.
The real difference lies in
their perspectives.
Take Liu Wei's disappearance
as an example.
Your viewpoint was
fixated on the assumption
that she must be in trouble.
You examine every angle
from this bias.
It narrows your vision
and hides other possibilities.
Deep down, your judgment
has been clouded.
From my perspective,
there's no evidence.
So we can't jump
to conclusions.
Instead, we should
address and crack
each questionable detail
to build our investigation.
Wait.
Let me jot this down.
These insights
are meaningful.
I can use them
in my videos.
I asked you whether
you'd be an officer
because of
your exceptional
deductive reasoning
and attention to detail.
If you structure
your perspective...
Never mind.
For your line of work,
that's all you need.
Wait, I want to improve.
I only have 100k followers.
What's this?
Intentional Homicide Case Studies?
Study it.
Think carefully.
Remember.
Try different angles.
(Oucheng Garden)
(The Logic Behind Truth)
You said you usually
reverse the projector.
Yeah.
I use that
as ambient lighting
and to remind myself
not to take things at face value.
Then why did you revert it?
It's another reminder
to avoid
restricting myself
to habitual perspectives.
Need some lighting?
(Truth)
Don't bother.
I just want to show you
my deduction.
About what?
About you.
About me?
There are
11 video clips.
The earliest
dates back to July 2018,
five months before your accident.
The latest one
is from September 2019.
That's 14 months,
minus one month in hospital.
No recordings from then.
That is
roughly once per month,
even after you're riding
in a wheelchair.
It seems
Zeng Jie is a real monster.
There are timestamps.
So I looked into
the pre- and post-abuse periods.
There were four instances
where you both acted
normally after he abused you.
For example,
he assaulted you
on October 21, 2018.
The next day,
you two went together
to an event,
dressed in formal attire.
He hit you
in the morning
on September 2nd, 2018,
and that evening, you posted
photos of
yourself dining with him
and other friends.
It's all for show.
We have to act normally.
Should I go around
wailing to everyone
about my misery?
I believe you.
But there's another possibility.
Care to hear it?
Domestic violence is illegal
and unforgivable.
But when Zeng Jie hit you,
you took no disciplinary action.
No police report,
no legal consultation,
not even a proper reprimand.
Instead, you quickly resumed normalcy
as if nothing had happened.
To use your own words,
"It's all for show."
Under your tolerance,
Zeng Jie became increasingly
agitated and violent.
Put differently,
you were the victim,
but you also
enabled his behavior.
Right,
I bought a bag today.
These years,
luxury goods have kept appreciating,
better than your fragile ceramics.
There he goes again.
Master Zeng, your temper
keeps getting worse.
What?
Want to hit me again?
(I don't know when exactly)
you first considered divorce,
but last October,
you took concrete steps.
You knew that you needed evidence
of his infidelity
to best protect
your assets.
So you spent some money
and found someone
to seduce Zeng Jie.
Because the intermediary
chose Liu Wei,
I got involved a year later.
(Rest assured.)
I'll do my job properly.
Wei seduced your husband,
while you seduced Zhang Ye.
"Seduce"
isn't quite the right word.
You exploited Zhang Ye.
You knew
he was still into you.
(You never)
(planned to file for divorce.)
(You just wanted)
(to capture Zhang Ye's attention.)
You showed him how vulnerable
and helpless you were
to convince him that
Zeng Jie had been abusing you.
Then later,
he'd become
your perfect ally.
Besides,
he was a capable
law firm partner.
But Liu Wei caused you trouble.
She betrayed you
and took money
from Zeng Jie.
Neither of you could do anything
but face the consequences.
(Liu Wei told Zeng Jie the truth.)
(So you couldn't use the affair)
(against Zeng Jie.)
(That's when)
you got murderous.
(On the night of the fire,)
(you left early to rest.)
(You said you were going home)
(but went to the third floor.)
(Zeng Jie thought he had hallucinated.)
(But he hadn't.)
After the party,
you went downstairs.
(You knew Zeng Jie had drunk heavily)
(and would surely stay.)
(So you moved the brazier)
(next to the sofa.)
(When the fire broke out,)
(Zeng Jie was alone in the studio.)
He'd had too much to drink
and could easily have died.
But to your surprise,
(his workplace)
(had organized a fire safety training)
(two days before)
(and given him an emergency escape kit.)
So he narrowly escaped death.
After that,
you couldn't find another chance
to make a move.
(Ironically, this fire)
(was leveraged for publicity)
(and made Zeng Jie
a master reborn from ashes.)
If you divorced him
right then,
Zeng Jie would lose some money
but still have a promising
and carefree future.
You couldn't bear that.
He had to go.
That's why you devised
a long-term plan
and pushed Zeng Jie
step by step into desperation.
Bai Xiaoling,
you're truly remarkable.
Go ahead.
I can't wait to hear the rest.
A month later, you had a car accident.
More precisely,
it was an accident that never
truly happened.
You even meticulously livestreamed
the entire accident
(Little Fairy)
(to your friend)
(via phone.)
You made the accident
appear convincing.
(The car crashed into a roadside ditch)
(and you were injured.)
But in reality,
your injuries were
extremely minor.
The wheelchair is real
but you're not disabled.
How I wish you're right.
Alright.
Let me explain
my deduction.
I obtained a used car
appraisal report.
(Used Vehicle Appraisal)
The evaluated car
was your vehicle.
Look.
It was sold last year
within two days.
The owner was a female driver
who drove into a ditch.
Only the engine cover
and chassis
have minor scratches.
The car is
perfectly fine.
The owner priced it shockingly low,
probably
traumatized by the accident.
The brakes weren't tampered with?
The brakes?
Of course not.
They are factory-original.
Still under warranty.
Who got the car here?
It's just an appraisal report.
Maybe I mistook the gas pedal
for the brake.
No way.
You know that.
And so do I.
That accident never
disabled you.
(You were hospitalized for a month,)
(spanning the New Year.)
(Zhang Ye visited you,)
(convinced that Zeng Jie
wanted you dead.)
Great story.
Continue.
After that,
your life became simple.
Of course,
only superficially.
(Almost every afternoon,)
(you'd be at the café,)
(reading on QQ Reader,)
(and go for groceries.)
(You're a pretty woman in a wheelchair.)
(So the merchants)
(quickly got to know you.)
(They knew you loved fish)
(and your husband loved meat.)
(They all thought you were optimistic)
(and caring.)
(In reality, Zeng Jie rarely came home.)
You kept buying meat
just to maintain your image
as a disabled, family-oriented,
and devoted wife
who dotes on her husband.
(You made them)
(your witnesses.)
(When public opinion)
(was boiling over,)
(they posted and reposted comments)
(to support you.)
(You fed)
(all that meat)
(to stray cats and dogs.)
Yeah.
I've followed you.
Reading at cafés,
getting groceries,
feeding leftovers to strays.
My daily routine
has become a conspiracy?
(Anatomy)
Looking familiar?
These were
the books saved
in your e-reader.
You must be mistaken.
I mostly
read novels.
Too bad I lost my reader,
or I'd show you.
Don't worry.
Your account still exists.
So your saved records remain intact.
Big Hui.
Are you saying
you suspect me?
Yes.
And there's more you should hear.
After being discharged,
you bought
six Damascus steel knives in six months.
The murder weapon
was the one
you took from home.
Of course,
you cleverly claimed beforehand
that Zeng Jie packed it himself
and even made the hotel staff
your witnesses.
Why did you get so many knives?
You were selecting the perfect one
while practicing the motions.
I also bought 12 steak knives
and two full kitchen knife sets.
A fruit knife is
easier to carry.
Makes sense.
So combining all this,
you think
I premeditated Zeng Jie's murder?
Three months ago,
I met you while investigating
Zeng Jie.
(You often)
(went to that cafe.)
(So I approached you.)
I know.
It hurt a bit
when I found out,
but I forgave you later.
No.
Bai Xiaoling.
You recognized me from the start.
You found out
when I mentioned
the Logic Behind Truth.
I'm a video content creator.
What kind of videos?
Mystery case analyses.
The Logic Behind Truth.
(Because I could help you)
uncover what you couldn't
easily learn about Zeng Jie.
The information about Lin Fang
was crucial.
What happened
to Lin Fang could
destroy Zeng Jie.
So you found Lin Shan
and gave him
a large amount of money.
I believe you asked him
to turn himself in
at a certain point
and expose Zeng Jie.
Actually,
I approached Zhang Xiaohong,
hoping she'd persuade Lin Shan.
But she turned me down.
I was shocked when Lin Shan
turned himself in.
But when I saw
your father's lawyer,
it all made sense.
(Lin Shan had been)
(Healthcare Center)
(part of your plan.)
(This connection)
helped me solve the final puzzle.
When you killed Zeng Jie at the hotel,
you were also stabbed twice.
It's reported those wounds came from
external force.
That means
you didn't stab yourself.
If my deductions
are correct,
you had
an accomplice in the hotel.
(Only the lobby)
(had cameras.)
(We can't find out)
(who's been in your room.)
You know what?
I obtained all the civilian
surveillance footage nearby
and finally identified your father.
He was cautious,
driving a borrowed car,
but made a mistake at one intersection.
He glanced out.
That's all?
That's all.
Great storytelling.
It's not about the storytelling.
Your planning was brilliant.
Do you know how exhausting
it is to analyze all this?
Big Hui,
you're truly impressive.
You got almost everything right.
But
you've only presented analysis
without evidence.
You flatter me.
I'm just an amateur.
Praise the professionals.
They've suspected you
long ago,
and launched a full investigation.
"They"?
That's right.
Bai Xiaoling,
turn yourself in.
Will you ride the wheelchair
or walk with your own legs?
Big Hui,
what a pity.
I didn't get to taste
the coffee you made.
Actually,
this is not what I wanted.
But it's beyond change now.
No, it's not.
And I'd like to
change it.
Isn't it your imagination
running wild?
(Li De)
Do you automatically assume
Zeng Jie is about to kill her?
I came here because
he might hurt
Bai Xiaoling.
Unbelievable.
Alright.
Have fun for now.
Keep watching them tomorrow.
But let me warn you.
Do not cross
any boundaries.
(Li De)
What now?
Big Hui.
This is urgent.
What?
We suspected that
Zeng Jie had tampered
with the brakes
of Bai's car.
Yeah.
That car was sold
as a used car
last year.
I got a report
from the car dealer.
The brakes were factory-original.
No replacement.
No damage.
Nothing's for sure.
But it shows
that something's wrong
with your deduction.
(The brakes)
suddenly failed.
Mount Qingcheng.
He doesn't have a reason
to mend your relationship.
We're mistaken.
Yeah.
I shouldn't be
calling you.
But this is urgent.
And you're right there.
Be careful
and try your best
to stall Bai Xiaoling.
He's not killing her.
She is
trying to kill him.
Coming.
Who is it?
Big Hui?
How come you're here?
This is great.
You're alive.
You're not killed.
Are you insane?
Get lost. Or I'll call the cops.
No need.
I've done that.
They'll be right here.
Xiaoling.
I've figured it all out.
Li De and I figured
everything out.
Listen.
This human trash
is not worth it.
What nonsense?
Get lost.
Did you kill Lin Fang?
Did you?
Listen.
Let's bring him to justice
for what he's done to Lin Fang.
Don't break the law
just to take revenge.
Xiaoling.
I know life has been hard.
You've suffered
a lot in the past year.
You've been
on your own all along.
But it's different now.
Me.
Li De.
Zhang Ye.
We're investigating.
We've obtained enough evidence.
Listen to me.
Don't break the law.
Lin Shan received
a lot of money
from you, right?
You know very well
this is the best way
to punish Zeng Jie.
Isn't that right?
If you kill him,
no matter how well
you've planned it,
it's still risky.
Li De was looking
for evidence that
Zeng Jie damaged the brakes.
But he found the report
on your car
from the car dealer.
You know exactly
what it says, right?
Your car
wasn't damaged.
The brakes were intact.
Before the accident,
that vehicle
had absolutely no issues.
The accident didn't injure you.
Your legs
are perfectly fine.
Xiaoling.
It's best to
let the police
solve this problem.
Let the law punish Zeng Jie.
It's far better than
stabbing him yourself.
I just want to kill him.
Yeah.
I know.
If I were you,
I'd want to kill him too.
But what next?
It only offers
a fleeting satisfaction.
Nothing else.
Deep down, you know
only the police
can bring Zeng Jie to justice.
Killing him yourself
is just a way to vent your hatred.
I know you're in pain.
I know you're angry.
I understand all that.
But I disapprove of your decision.
Xiaoling.
As your friend,
I don't want you
to punish a villain
and end up
a criminal yourself.
Let's be rational.
Okay?
I've always been rational.
You've been meticulously planning
to kill him with cold calculation.
But you're not rational
about the bigger picture.
Zeng Jie ruined your youthful years,
but that's in the past.
You still have a bright future.
You're so young
and pretty.
And you're loved.
Do you have to
give up everything?
Your plan is not
that flawless.
Think about it.
Li De
and I
have both uncovered flaws.
Amateurs can't outplay
professionals.
I know
your father is waiting
somewhere right now.
Do you want to
drag him into this?
To punish Zeng Jie,
do you
and your father
have to sacrifice everything?
Is it worth it?
Trust me.
This is for the best.
♪Within the dim lights
there is a bright view♪
♪Some whisperings
are louder than screams♪
♪The drowning sea
is not the sky in dark blue♪
♪In this world you'll never see through♪
♪Cut all that annoyance♪
♪I'm into my enjoyment♪
♪No sympathetic words
rolled out of my mouth♪
♪'Cause once you start, can't recall♪
♪Soon I will hypnotize
the sourness in your eyes♪
♪Follow my insight, don't fall behind♪
♪The story must be told♪
♪Questioning where my soul♪
♪Don't you feel♪
♪It's running from your throat♪
♪So hypnotize before we pull the fight♪
♪Eye to eye♪
♪Before you spill the lie♪
♪So hypnotize before we pull the fight♪
♪Eye to eye♪
♪Before you spill the lie♪
♪So hypnotize before we pull the fight♪
♪Eye to eye♪
♪Before you spill the lie♪
(Zhang Ye)
Ms. Juan.
This is Zhang Ye.
Let me report to you.
Zeng Jie's sentencing
won't happen immediately.
But it's almost certain.
I will
keep you updated about the details.
Want to reply?
I don't want you to see me off.
You kept telling me
to study abroad.
Why?
Now that I'm leaving,
you start nagging me?
Rest assured.
I'll study hard
when I'm out there.
I won't be the same.
You don't know
your daughter
at all, Dad.
Enough.
Remember.
First,
take care.
Second,
keep my mom company.
Third,
although I've forgiven you,
you must keep doing your best
or I'll be disappointed.
Cheers.
Zeng Jie
doesn't even remember
where he buried Lin Fang.
They dug around
for 20 days
and confirmed
that it was her body
through DNA matching with Lin Shan.
Is Zeng sentenced?
Not so soon.
He's in the detention center.
His reputation is ruined.
He can't get away with it.
What about Lin Shan?
He's charged with extortion.
And he unknowingly
harbored the criminal.
But
he turned himself in
and reported Zeng Jie.
So, he will
get a lighter sentence.
Have you seen
Bai Xiaoling lately?
No.
Didn't you
visit her?
No.
I'm done.
My tongue got numb
from kissing up to her.
I'm tired of it.
But
you did help her a lot.
You know what?
I always thought
she was a dumb,
pretty woman.
Now, I've realized who is
the dumb one.
I'm the dumb one.
She's pretty,
smart, bold,
and enduring.
I used to think
I was her savior.
But now I've realized
that I'm nothing like a savior.
I'm just playing a secondary role
in her life.
It has always been
and will remain that way.
No.
Not even a secondary role.
I'm an extra.
I feel too embarrassed
to see her now.
I have no dignity.
Ye.
You never had dignity.
Get lost.
Cheers.
Bro, you seriously
hurt my feelings.
You know?
I have closed
the chapter on my youth.
I'm Big Hui.
I'm Tracy.
This is...
- The Logic Behind Truth.
Cut.
Thought you were alone.
We haven't dined out once
since your promotion.
I've been swamped with work.
I'd rather sleep more.
Besides, didn't I lend you
the car for filming?
I did help.
Is she even fit
to make videos?
She's amazing.
Great writing skills.
Exceptional analytical ability
and critical thinking.
She's even mastering photography.
So impressive?
You have no idea.
I gained over 100k followers
last month. Most came for her.
My ad rates
have nearly doubled.
Congratulations.
She's perfect in every way,
except for one thing.
That's not fair!
You agreed to give me
30% of the ad revenue.
Why do I care
about the costs?
Be reasonable!
Filming has a cost.
Post-production,
field trips for footage,
meals, gas...
These have costs.
You should have said that.
It's common sense.
We've been
filming till now.
What's this meal
we're having?
You're treating me
as my boss.
Why should I pay for your meal?
It's part of the cost.
I'm being fair.
I'm not trying to cheat.
Why do you need
so much cash?
You have no expenses.
Thanks.
I never realized
you're so penny-pinching.
I'm buying a house.
After my surgery,
I had about 200k left.
I need 500k in two years
for the down payment.
So ambitious.
Lin Shan will be out in two years.
I want to surprise him.
Where you going?
To the restroom.
If we're splitting costs,
that means
I'm paying too.
From now on,
we mustn't splurge on meals.
Three dishes for two people
is too extravagant.
How is it extravagant...
Besides,
we should avoid
fancy places like this.
It looks pricey.
What are you looking at?
- No more fancy restaurants.
- Check, please.
Street stalls are better anyway.
Put theirs on my bill.
Hey!
Thanks.
That Monet kid is new here.
He even got into Caorong University.
He's working to pay tuition.
(Zeng Jie: Intentional homicide,
life imprisonment)
(Lin Shan: Harboring, Extortion,
3 years imprisonment, CNY20k fine)
(Bai Xiaoling: Attempted homicide,
5 years imprisonment)
(Bai Mingfeng: Evidence tampering,
6-month detention with 1-year probation)
(Zhang Ye: Rumor-mongering,
stripped of license)
(Yang Zhenghui: Rumor-mongering,
10-day detention and CNY500 fine)
(In subsequent investigations,
Tang Wei, alias Liu Wei:)
(Convicted of extortion,
6 years imprisonment, CNY50k fine)
(Artist Village under inspection
for illegal art replication activities.)
(The factory was closed down.
The case remains under investigation.)
That's a wrap on Blemish Flaw!
Happy New Year!
(The Logic Behind Truth)
Like this.
We'll leave the car here.
But given our relationship,
this isn't appropriate.
Or maybe I should tell him...
What should I do?
Should I go pay my respects to him?
Sorry.
Retake.
Big Hui, did you follow us here?
You're still alive.
You haven't been killed.
Are you insane?
What's wrong? It's fine.
Sorry.
It's fine.
Did you follow us here?
Are you insane?
I'll call the cops.
♪Cut all that annoyance♪
You've been meticulously planning...
You've been
meticulously planning...
What nonsense?
Get out.
Get lost.
Did you kill Lin Fang?
Did you?
Trust me.
This is for the best.
You're so loud.
Cut.
He's so annoying.
So awkward.
If I'm not embarrassed, you will be.
You seriously hurt my feelings.
I have closed
the chapter on my youth.
♪Follow my insight, don't fall behind♪
♪The story must be told♪
♪Questioning where my soul♪
Let's drink.
I was shocked
when Lin Shan turned himself in.
♪So hypnotize before we pull the fight♪
Sorry, I forgot my lines.
♪Eye to eye♪
We've been filming all morning.
Isn't this meal part of the cost?
Wait, no...
Alright, wrap it up.
♪Before you spill the lie♪
You're walking like a normal person.
Your heel and the stick shouldn't
touch the ground simultaneously.
You need to practice.
Yeah.
- Grip the cane.
- Yeah.